How's it going?
We just talked about riding the board.
Remember I told you it's one of the funniest that I see people do?
It's because they really don't know how to bounce up and down, up and down with the diving board.
So, what I've got right now for you is a drill that you can practice over and over and over again so you get comfortable bouncing on the board, OK.
I would suggest, before you do anything, even trying a dive, you really get comfortable and really get used to just bouncing on the end of the board, OK.
So, I'm going to go out to the end of the board, and I'll explain to you what we're going to do.
OK, right now I'm standing on the end of the board.
You notice that it's bouncing up and down.
What I'm actually doing, very poorly, because I'm facing backwards, is riding the board right now, OK.
Here's what you can do to practice riding the board.
I'm going to face out to the pool.
All you're going to do is bounce up and down, up and down.
Try to do it 3 times in a row.
What you're concentrating on is pushing the board all the way down, and coming up and rising up with the board, OK.
The second time you land, you should feel a nice smooth transition, OK.
If you've fallen in to the water, you're doing a bad job at riding the board, OK.
Here's what it looks like.
OK, if you can do that 3 times in a row, you're on your way to riding the board.